What the hell
did you just say?
A lowborn like
you dares threaten me?
Just friendly advice.
Don't play both sides.
You'll fall hard.
Fall from where?
You think you’re
still the Carter heir?
You’ve been discarded.
Redmond owns House Carter now.
The Carter name has never meant a damn thing to me.
Sour grapes from the man who couldn’t claim the throne.
Believe what you want.
But after today, everyone on
Golantis
will know my real name.
And you will curse the
day you were born blind.
Insolent piece of shit!
I’ll teach you
some manners right now!
Your organs are turning to stone.
Keep raging like this, you'll die.
How… how do you know that?
I know everything.
You planted spies in my castle!
That diagnosis came directly
from the Royal Oracle last night!
How else could you know?!
I never imagined
you’d sink this low.
Spying on your
own fiancée’s mother?
How pathetic.
Gods, that’s disgusting.
Lowborns. I can't believe Lady Livia's being forced
to marry this filth.
You sick perverted mole!
Confess right now,
or I'll have the guards
skin you alive in the dungeons!